Welcome to FanForce AI, where everyone earns rewards from their predictions combining real sports data with defined mechanics.
欢迎来到FanForce AI，每个人都能从预测中获得奖励，结合真实体育数据与确定机制。
I will show you how predictions work in just a few steps.
我将用几个简单步骤向您展示预测是如何运作的。
First, let's connect the administrator's wallet.
首先，让我们连接管理员的钱包。
You can see we're now connected to the testnet.
可以看到现在我们正连接着测试网。
Let's navigate to the admin interface to create two teams.
来到管理员界面，创建两支队伍。
To simplify the demonstration, I'm only entering three basic data points: historical win rate, average player age, and injury count.
为了简化演示，我只录入了三项基础数据：历史胜率、球员平均年龄以及伤病人数。
Now creating the second team.
创建第二支队伍。
Next, we'll use these two teams to create a match.
接下来我们用这两支队伍创建一场比赛。
Creating a match requires smart contract logic, so you'll see a wallet transaction request appear.
创建比赛需要通过智能合约逻辑，所以这里会出现钱包的交易请求。
After clicking confirm, we wait for the contract creation.
点击确认之后，等待合约创建。
You can see the match has been successfully created and we can now enter the battle page.
可以看到目前的比赛已经创建成功，并且可以进入对战页面。
Now we're entering a pre-configured match where you can see clear data display for each team.
现在我们进入一场已经配置好的比赛，你可以看到每支队伍都有清晰的数据展示。
In this demo, we've implemented intelligent rule analysis to simulate AI analysis.
在这个演示中，我们实现了智能规则分析来模拟AI分析。
When we click AI analysis, we can get the final team analysis conclusion through our data dimensions.
当我们点击AI分析的时候，可以通过我们的数据维度得到最终的队伍分析结论。
Now let's demonstrate the complete user flow.
现在演示用户全流程。
First, through the administrator account, we'll inject rewards into this match as the platform's incentive source.
首先，通过管理员账户，我们向这场比赛注入奖池，作为平台方的激励来源。
We're depositing 5 test tokens and waiting for transaction processing.
我们存入5个测试币，等待交易处理。
Great! The page now shows 5 test tokens have been injected as platform rewards.
好！现在页面可以看到已经注入了5个测试币作为平台奖励。
Next, we'll switch to User A, connect their wallet account, and enter the betting interface.
接下来我们切换到用户A，连接钱包账户，进入到投注界面。
User A chooses to support this team to win, enters 3 test tokens as stake, and confirms the contract transaction.
用户A选择支持这一队伍获胜，输入3个测试币作为质押，确认合约的交易。
Great! The transaction is complete.
好！交易已经完成。
Note that the platform charges a 5% fee as transaction costs.
注意，平台方会收取5%的费用作为手续费。
Now let's switch to User B and connect User B's wallet.
接下来切换到用户B，连接用户B的钱包。
You can see User B has connected successfully and is starting to bet.
可以看到用户B已经连接成功，开始投注。
Betting 2 test tokens to support the other team, waiting for contract transaction confirmation.
投注两个测试币，支持另外一支队伍，等待合约的交易确认。
Perfect! Now the page shows both teams have received certain amounts of test token bets.
好！现在页面中两支队伍分别被投注了一定数额的测试币。
Let's switch the wallet back to the administrator.
让我们将钱包切换到管理员这边。
Connecting administrator account.
连接管理员账户。
The administrator announces the match winning team.
管理员宣布比赛获胜队伍。
Confirming through the contract.
通过合约确认。
So the match winner has been written into the contract.
那么比赛获胜方就被写入了合约中。
We can see from the interface that our winner has been determined.
我们可以从界面上看到，我们的赢家已经诞生。
Next, it's time to switch to both users to claim their rewards.
接下来该切换到两个用户来领取奖励。
The interface shows our reward claiming formula.
界面上是我们领取奖励的公式。
According to the logic, User A predicted successfully and will receive their principal plus 70% of the reward pool, minus the 5% platform fee.
根据逻辑，用户A预测成功，会获得本金加奖励池中70%的份额，减去5%的平台提成。
The final amount comes to approximately 6 test tokens.
得到最终的金额就是6个左右的测试币。
You can see they have successfully claimed their reward.
可以看到他已经成功领取奖励。
The page has updated accordingly.
页面也发生相应的变化。
Similarly, let's go to User B.
同理，我们来到用户B。
After connecting User B's wallet, we see the balance is now 0.97.
连接用户B钱包之后，我们看到金额现在剩0.97。
User B's prediction failed, but under our rules they can still claim approximately 3.2 test tokens.
用户B预测失败，但可以在规则下领取3.2个左右的测试币。
Processing through wallet transaction, clicking confirm.
通过钱包交易，点击确认。
You can see they have successfully claimed their reward.
可以看到他已经领取到了他的奖励。
That concludes our complete demonstration.
以上就是所有的演示流程。
Thank you for watching.
感谢各位观看。